const triviaQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How big of a loser do I think you are?",
        options: ["very big" , "bigger than the universe", "the biggest one you’ve ever met" , "wdym? i’m not a loser"],
        answer: 1
    }, 
    {
        question: "How long do you think it took me to make this game?",
        options: ["2-3 days" , "1 week", "A WHOLE MONTH" , "2 weeks only"],
        answer: 1 
    }, 
    {
        question: "If i had to give our friendship a color, what color do you think i’d give it? \nYou represent the first color, while i represent the second color",
        options: ["blue-green" , "matcha green - baby pink", "teal - purple" , "golden - brown "],
        answer: 2
    }, 
    {
        question: "What do you think i’d rate you on a scale from 1-10 (as a person)",
        options: ["I’M OBVIOUSLY A 10" , "i’m not delusional, so definitely a 0", "pls be 8 atleast" , "6/10 "],
        answer: 3
    }, 
    {
        question: "if i were to describe you in one word, what do you think it would be?",
        options: ["iconic bitch" , "best friend", "questionable " , "little brother "],
        answer: 3
    }, 
    {
        question: "if i had to compare you to an animal, which one do you think it would be?",
        options: ["mosquito" , "fat and lazy cat", "ugly pug (dog)" , "hamster (cuz ur dumb) "],
        answer: 3
    }, 
    {
        question: "if i were making a movie, what role do you think i’d give you?",
        options: ["cleaning boy who doesn’t get a role" , "side character who dies first", "irritating bestie who yaps a lot" , "main character (ur delusional) "],
        answer: 0
    }, 
    {
        question: "how much patience do you think i have when you do stupid shit?",
        options: ["barely any" , "a saint-like amount", "you pretend you do, but you don’t" , "you only encourage me cuz its funny "],
        answer: 1
    }, 
    {
        question: "What do you think is your worst habit?",
        options: ["replying to you as-if you’re a chatbot" , "being delusional", "never being on time" , "nagging you even though i’m worse "],
        answer: 0
    }, 
    {
        question: "what memory do you think is my fav thing about you? ",
        options: ["i reply fast" , "i listen to skz with you", "i tell you amazing gossip" , "i always listen to you yap "],
        answer: 2
    }
]